slideroom.com 2019-12-06

# SlideRoom - Privacy Policy

SlideRoom Technologies Inc. (“Company”) is a business to business service provider providing applicant tracking systems (ATS) to almost one thousand institutional customers across university admissions, HR, grants, and other important areas. As such we hand all personal data as a data processor, and follow the directions of our client, who remains the data controller. 

This statement applies with respect to the information that we collect from the Product Website at [http://www.SlideRoom.com](http://www.slideroom.com/) and Accounts provided to our Clients and their applicants. Amendments to this statement will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof.

###  I. INFORMATION COLLECTED

We collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities through your IP address, computer settings or most-recently visited URL. We may also ask you to provide your name, address, email, and phone number and other personally identifiable items defined by each SlideRoom customer you elect to submit an application to, in order to fulfill your application requirements. We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us, by, for example, filling out a SlideRoom-hosted application or registration form.

###  II. USE OF INFORMATION

We will only use the information you provide to us for the purpose for which such information was provided. We may also use this information to deliver to you information about our company and site administration. If we ever were to engage in any onward transfers of your data with third parties for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized, we would provide you with an opt-out choice to limit the use and disclosure of your personal data. SlideRoom is a data processor and as such works with the data controller, to ensure security and privacy for all SlideRoom users. If you ever submit a payment through SlideRoom, please note that SlideRoom does not directly process or store your financial account information – instead, we use a reputable third party company to collect and process your payment information. Rest assured, however, that we have taken steps to ensure that the Payment Processing Company protects personal information it collects from you in compliance with our Privacy Policy. 

###  III. USE OF IP ADDRESS

We use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website.

###  IV. USE OF COOKIES

When you view our Website we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard drive nor steal information. Rather, they help you navigate a Website as easily as possible. We use cookies to store that users are logged in and to gather aggregate information via Google Analytics.

SlideRoom uses third party vendor re-marketing tracking cookies, including the Google Adwords tracking cookie. Third party vendors will place cookies on web browsers in order to serve ads based on past website visits or engagement with our content. These cookies may be used to show ads to you across the Internet. As always we respect your privacy and are not collecting any personally identifiable information through the use of any third party remarketing system. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting your [Google Ad Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads).

###  V. SECURITY

SlideRoom uses industry standard security measures to protect the loss, misuse, disclosure, and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take all commercially reasonable steps to secure your personal information.

To protect your SlideRoom account, keep your password confidential. You are responsible for the activity that happens on or through your SlideRoom account. Try not to reuse your SlideRoom account password on any other application or website. 

If you enter your password in an external website and it's compromised, someone could try to sign in to your SlideRoom account with the same information. Don't write it down, send it via email, or tell anyone. SlideRoom will never email you to ask for your password or other sensitive information. 

If you learn of any unauthorized use of your password or SlideRoom account, please contact SlideRoom at [support@slideroom.com](mailto:support@slideroom.com) immediately. 

###  VI. ONWARD TRANSFER

SlideRoom may be required to disclose personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU and Swiss individuals received pursuant to the Privacy Shield Principles, SlideRoom is liable unless we can prove we were not a party giving rise to the damages.

SlideRoom will only disclose your personal information with the organization that you are applying to, whom you purposefully select to submit that information to. Whenever your application is submitted to third party, that organization and only that organization will be able to view all information associated with your SlideRoom account, as well as all information included in your surveys, applications, or forms you submit to that organization.

If we ever were to engage in any onward transfers of your data with any third parties for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized, we would provide you with an opt-out choice to limit the use and disclosure of your personal data.

### VII. EU DATA PROTECTION

SlideRoom complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. SlideRoom has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.

To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>

In compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield, SlideRoom commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact SlideRoom by emailing to [support@slideroom.com](mailto:support@slideroom.com) or by mailing notice to our physical office:

SlideRoom  
Attn: Privacy Shield Issues  
12001 N. Central Expy, Suite 1025  
Dallas, TX 75243

SlideRoom has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU Privacy Shield, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by SlideRoom, please visit the BBB EU Privacy Shield web site at <http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/file-a-complaint/> for more information and to file a complaint.

If your Privacy Shield complaint cannot be resolved through the above channels, under certain conditions, you may invoke binding arbitration for some residual claims not resolved by other redress mechanisms. See Privacy Shield Annex 1 at https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introductionSlideRoom is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

SlideRoom is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

### VIII. RIGHT TO ACCESS

The SlideRoom service allows its users the right to access their data or modify information previously provided. Prior to submission, applicants may access their data and content from their user account in the ‘my account’ section of the SlideRoom website. SlideRoom acknowledges that EU and Swiss individuals have the right to access the personal information that we maintain about them. 

Any applicant who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete their own inaccurate data, should direct this query to the organization they have applied to. If data has been submitted to an organization, they are responsible for the requested actions regarding such data. SlideRoom clients must make SlideRoom aware of all applicant requests to delete user data or content. SlideRoom clients should contact SlideRoom directly with any client user data access, edit, or delete requests. If requested to remove or delete data, SlideRoom will respond within a reasonable timeframe. 

### IX. PUBLIC FORUMS

This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### X. CONTACTING US

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you may contact [support@slideroom.com](mailto:support@slideroom.com).
